ABDUL AZIZ TARIQ

Front End Web Developer

about me

Software Engineer having an experience of two years in Front End Web Development and Web Designing. Looking to leverage my knowledge and experience and utilize my skills into a role as Front End Developer.

contact



+92-342-0652369



abdulaziz652369@gmail.com



https://frontendaz.me



Github.com/abdulaziz65



Linkedin.com/in/Abdulaziz-110227194

EDUCATION

Bs Software Engineering

University of Gujrat Gujrat 2018 - 2022

Intermedia (Pre-Engineering)

Punjab College of Commerce Wazirabad 2015 - 2017

SKILLS

Web Development

HTML5, CSS3 **Bootstrap** JavaScript WordPress

Web Designing

Adobe Photoshop Adobe XD

Adobe illustrator Figma

Adobe After Effects

CERTIFICATIONS

E-Rozgar Technical Course/2021 TEVTA Gujrat

Front End Development Tools: Bootstrap 4 / 2021 Coursera / Learning Platform

professional experience

2020 - Present

Front End Web Developer

Up Upwork.com

Web development using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap and WordPress

2019 - Present

WordPress Developer



fi Fiverr.com

Experienced in creating blog websites, E-Commerce website, Real Estate Business Websites